- Nothing's happening - Watch
- 什么也没发生 - 看着
Ah
啊!
Ooh Ah,what--
哦 啊 什么--
I'm so sorry,emily
对不起 Emily
What was that
是什么东西?
Don't you recognize a rocket when you see one
你没看出那是个火箭吗?
I--I was merely demonstrating a physics law
我 我只是在证明一个物理学定律
I--I--I didn't meant to hit-- oh,show me
- 我 我没想打... - 让我看看
All right
好吧
Uh... well,turn around,please
呃...好 请转过身去
Turn around
转身
Yeah,he's not gonna show you... how it's done
是的 他可不想让你看到...是怎么弄的
A magician doesn't reveal his secrets
魔术师不会暴露他的秘密
But I thought you said it was physics
但我以为你是说物理学
Physics...magic
物理...魔力
Trust me
相信我
It will not do you any good to argue with him
跟他争没什么便宜好占
All right,all right,turn back and observe
好啦 好啦 转回来 注意看
All: Oh
哦!
Physics magic
物理魔法
Yes,sir
是的 长官
Reid,we talked about this
Reid 我们说过的
I'm sorry,sir
对不起 长官
Really starting to get some distance on those
这次真的弹得比较远了
So he does have a sense of humor
看来他还是有点幽默感的
Sometimes
有时吧
Hey,where's morgan
嗨  Morgan哪儿去了?
In chicago
在芝加哥
He goes there every year for his mother's birthday
他每年都去给他妈妈过生日
[Camera clicks] You're sure she's got enough butter
你确定她的黄油够用?
You know if sarah doesn't put it on the list she doesn't need it
要是Sarah没列在单子上 那她就不需要
- She doesn't make mistakes
她从不犯错
Looking good
看看是谁来了 看上去不错嘛
I mean,damn
我是说 该死的
You fillin' out all good in all the right places,aren't you
看来你在哪儿都混得不错嘛 是不是?
Step off,rodney
退后 Rodney
Desiree,get in the car
Desiree 上车
- Come on,derek,it's nothing
- 别这样 Derek 没事的 - 我说了上车去
Heh heh
嘿嘿
That's ok,baby
好吧 宝贝
I'll get wit' you a little later,huh
等会再给你你想要的
Yeah,in your dreams
恩 你做梦去吧
Ooh,most definitely
哦 真干脆
All night long,baby girl,huh
夜可长着呢 宝贝
You better step off before I make you wish you never walked up on me
你最好退后点 不要等我让你后悔走到我跟前
What,you think you a bad-ass now because they pay you to wear that gun,mr Fbi
怎么 因为干上了能带枪的活儿 你就是个人物了吗 FBI先生?
Rodney,I proved a long time ago I don't need a gun to take you out
Rodney 很久以前我就证明过 搞定你不需要枪
Past history,that's a dangerous thing for you to count on,my friend
朋友 不要凭当年勇 那很危险
Walk away
走开
Ha ha ha
哈哈哈
Des,I'll get at you a little later,huh
Des 我过会儿去找你
Go to hell
滚远点
Bitch
贱人
You all right
你没事?
Just a fool
不过是个蠢货
come on,I'm taking you home
来吧 我带你回家
There's something I gotta do
我有点事要做
That's the man,james
就是这样 James
Way to run a route
跑位跑得不错
Nice job,nice job
干得好 干得好
Come on,damien
Damien 加把劲
You call that pass coverage
这也算防传球吗?
You bite on the inside route every damned time
每次你都想走内线
Ok,let's bring it in,boys
好了 把球装好 孩子们
Get your helmets,let's go
拿上你们的头盗 走吧
[Sighs] You pushed off on that last catch
最后那次接球你推人了
Man,you weren't close enough to push off of
你没靠得那么近 我推不着你
I blew you away
我打败了你
I could cover your ass all day long
我能一直防住你的
- Man,kiss it all day long
防个屁
Hey,hey,hey
嗨嗨嗨
Knock it off
停
That's enough
够了
You did push off,james,on your second cut,with your inside hand
你的确推人了 James 在第二节时 用靠近他的那只手
Damn right
就是的
Hey
嗨
It's not the push-off that beat you,though
但不是因为推人你才输的
That's happening off the line
那是在场下发生的
Who are you
你是谁?
What's up,derek
怎么样了 Derek?
What's up,youngster
你呢 小伙子
I see you're still shakin' and bakin'
我看你还在无所事事
I get what I can
我能做什么就做什么
Damien,this is derek morgan
Damien 这位是Derek Morgan
The derek morgan
那个Derek Morgan?
Fbi derek morgan
FBI Derek Morgan
Just derek,brother
叫我Derek 兄弟
Nice to meet you,man
见到你很高兴
- Yeah
是呀
Get over there
快离开
Get over there Come on
快离开 快点
Take him wit' you Get over there
带着他快离开
Get the hell outta here
快滚开这儿
You wanna mess with somebody
你们不想找死吧?
Morgan: Uh-oh
哦 哦
1,2,3... happy birthday to ya
1 2 3...祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to ya
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday
生日快乐
Go ahead,momma
来吧 妈妈
Did you make this yourself
你自己做的吗?
Uh,sarah helped me
Sarah帮了一把
Momma,they wouldn't let me help so I don't know how good it's gonna taste
妈妈 他们不让我插手 所以我也不知道味道如何
Oh,no,no,no
哦 不 不
- You remember that christmas fiasco of 1994
- 你还记得1994年圣诞节的惨败吗? - 我记得
Whatever,that was 12 years ago
再怎么说 也是12年前的事了
Let it go
就算了吧
No,no,we still get cards from the fire department
不 不 我现在还能收到消防局的卡片呢
Momma,momma,you see how they treat your baby boy
妈妈 妈妈 你看到他们怎么对待你的宝贝男孩了吧
You be good to your brother
对你兄弟好一点
Uh-huh,what she said
啊啊 听听她怎么说的
No,no,no,you got the baby part right
不 不 不 你只是个小宝贝吧?
Ok,you know what
好 看我的
Ok now... [Shrieking and laughter] Ok,wish,wish
- 好吧 现在... - 好啦 许愿 许愿
Make a wish
许个愿
Morgan: There it is
好啦
[Camera clicks] Just like the others
跟另几个一样
Hey
嗨
Stan
Stan
I'm gonna lock that son of a bitch up
我要把那狗娘养的关起来
Shouldn't we call the powers that be
我们不该给当局打个电话吗?
This is big,stan
这是大事 Stan
To hell with that
去他的吧
What is it
这是什么?
Here
这个
It's a remote starter,mom
是个遥控车锁 妈妈
You hit that button right there and it starts your car from inside the house
你按一下这个按钮 就能在家里给车起火
Why would I do that
有什么用?
So it's nice and warm when you get in it
这样你上车的时候 就可以很暖和了
- Really
- 真的吗? - 是的
No more cold cars in the winter,mom
冬天不用再进到冰冷的车里了 妈妈
I would like one for christmas
我圣诞节也想要一个
Not for that bucket you drive
你那辆烂车就算了吧
Shut up
住嘴
get outta here
出去吧
[Laughter] We miss you around here,baby
我们都很想你 宝贝
I know
我知道
Your sisters wish you were around more
你的姐妹们也希望你能多来几次
You know the unit I work for is only out of virginia,you know that
你知道我工作的单位在维吉尼亚之外
Well...you're careful,right
好吧...你会小心的是吗?
I lost your dad
我失去了你爸爸
I can't lose you
不能再失去你了
You won'T
不会的
Good
那就好
'Cause you owe me some grand babies
因为你还没让我抱上孙子呢
Oh,come on,mom
哦 别这样 妈妈
[Knocking on door] Oh,look at that,saved by the bell
哦 看看 敲门声救了我
Phew
唉
A bunch of them
我还要好几个呢
Oh,come on,mom,stop
哦 妈妈 别说了 这是怎么回事?
Gordinski
Gordinski
You armed
你带枪了?
Excuse me
对不起
Are you wearing a gun
你带枪了吗?
No
没有
Not right now
现在没有
Then turn around
那转过身去
This is some kind of sick joke,right
这不是什么玩笑吧?
Don't make us get physical
别让我们动粗
It'll only make it worse for your family
这对你家人不好
You're under arrest,derek
你被捕了 Derek
how secrets deep
秘密有多深？
how secrets become dark
秘密如何变得黑暗
that's in the nature of secrets
这就是秘密的本质
" Writer,cory doctorow
科利・多克托罗 作家
You know,you better have a real good reason for doing that in front of my family
你最好有足够的理由在我家人面前这么做
You gonna tell me the charges now
你要现在告诉我对我的指控是什么
Oh,I bet if you think real hard you'll be able to figure it out,derek
哦 我想如果你好好想想 也许能想出来 Derek
Uncuff him
解开他的手拷
Agent morgan
Morgan探员
You'll always just be derek to me
对我而言你永远只是Derek
And you'll always be a racist son of a bitch to me
对我而言你永远只是种族歧视的混蛋
Right,derek
是的 Derek
That's all it is
就是这么回事
Then what,man
你还要怎么样?
[Chuckles] Man,I should have done this a long time ago
我早该这么做了
What the hell are you talking about
你他妈的在说什么?
Sit down
坐下
[Chuckles] Oh,wow
哦 哇
There isn't gonna be a hole deep enough to bury your career
你会因此毁掉你的职业生涯
What's wrong with you,man
你有毛病吗?
You know I'm an fbi agent
你知道我是FBI探员
Well,then you should be fairly aware of your rights
那你应该很清楚你的权力
Do you want a lawyer
你想要个律师吗?
I'm not some punk kid you can scare anymore,gordinski
我不再是小混混了 你吓不到我 Gordinski
Tough guy... you want a lawyer Yes or no
难搞的家伙...你倒底要不要律师?
I want a phone call
我想打个电话
Local
市内的?
I need to call my supervisor at fbi headquarters in quantico
我要打电话给FBI匡蒂科总部的主管
Agent hotchner
Hotchner探员
He's already getting a call
他已经接到电话了
There has to be a mistake
一定是搞错了
Yes
是的
Of course
当然
We're on our way
我们这就赶过去
[Sighs] This is ssa hotchner,
我是高级特别探员Hotchner
I need an emergency recall of agents reid,prentiss,jareau and penelope garcia as well
我要紧急召回Reid  Prentiss Jareau探员和Penelope Garcia
Yeah--uh,yes,I'll call him myself,thank you
好 呃 我自己打给他 谢谢
Jason,it's hotch,we've got to get to chicago,morgan's been arrested
Jason 我是Hotch 我们要去芝加哥 Morgan被逮捕了
Homicide
谋杀
Righ I can wait as long as you guys can
你们能等多久 我也能
Did you get some sleep
有睡过吗?
You know I didn'T
你知道我没有
Slept like a baby,myself
我睡得很香
Didn't even wanna get out of bed
甚至都不想醒过来
Really
真的?
So that wasn't your donut-eatin' ass on the other side of that glass all night,then,huh
那么整夜在玻璃对面晃的那 被甜甜圈喂肥的屁股不是你的喽
Here you go
给你
You want the other ones
还要其他的嘛?
No,just this one right now
不 暂时就这个
[Laughs] Come on,man
得了吧 老兄
You gotta be kidding me,right
你耍我的吧?
Pretend you went home and slept,put an empty box with my name on it on a table right in front of me
假装自己回家睡觉 再在我桌前 放只写了我名字的空箱子
The fbi invented this stuff,you simple bastard
这是FBI发明的 你这个蠢蛋
We teach it
是我们教的
What's this
这是什么?
It's yesterday
昨天的
You're following me
你跟踪我
Whose grave is that
那是谁的坟墓?
Why would you be following me
你干吗跟踪我?
Whose grave
谁的坟墓
You know I don't know his name
你知道我不认识他
You paid to bury him,didn't you
你付钱埋了他 对吗?
The neighborhood did
是社区付的
But you led the collection
但是你发起捐款的
So
所以呢?
And you visit him a lot
你经常探望他
Every time I come home
每次回家
Is there something wrong with that
这有什么错?
[Chuckles] What,you got a crush on me all of a sudden,gordinski
怎么 你突然盯上我了 Gordinski?
Ok,that's me at the youth center tossing a ball around with a couple of kids
没错 我在青少年中心 跟几个孩子一起玩球
You did a little more than that
可不止那些
This is about you giving one of them a ride home,one of the boys
你还送其中一个回家 其中一个男孩
Yeah
对
Yeah,I did
没错
This kid named,um,damien
这孩子叫 呃 Damien
His place was on the way to my mother'S
正好到我妈妈家顺路
So what,man
那又怎么了 老兄
Damien walters,D O A
Damien Walters 当场死亡
Oh,no
噢 不
Somebody killed him
有人杀了他
Not somebody,derek
不是别人 Derek
You think I did this
你以为是我
Special agent hotchner,fbi
FBI特别探员Hotchner
I'm looking for detective... gordinski
我找...Gordinski探长
I got this,chuck
让我来 Chunk
How you guys doing
你们好?
Wally dennison,cpd
芝加哥警局Wally Dennison
Where's agent morgan
Morgan探员在哪儿?
Detective gordinski's in with the suspect now
Gordinski探长跟嫌犯就在里面
I need to see him
我要见他
When my partner's finished talking to him
等我搭档训完话后吧
I have your superintendent's personal cell number,
我知道你们局长的私人电话
and in the interest of not running roughshod over another police agency
为了避免对另一个警察部门 太过颐指气使
I've resisted calling him so far
我至今都忍着没打给他
I need to see agent morgan now
我要立刻见到Morgan探员
I'll get gordinski
我去告诉Gordinski
He's the,uh,primary
他是 呃 上司
I don't like them calling him a suspect
我不喜欢他们称他嫌犯
Me neither
我也是
You're the last person anyone saw with my victim
有人证明 你是受害人接触的最后一人
You recognize him
你认识他吗?
Found in an alley four years ago
四年前在小巷发现的
Still unidentified
身份还未确认
John doe
无名氏
Just like that kid whose grave you visit every time you come to chicago
就像你每次回芝加哥 去扫墓的孩子一样
Another boy
另一个男孩
Just after you left the city
就在你离开之后
This is crazy
简直疯了
No kidding
不是玩笑
Look,man,rodney harris
听着 老兄 Rodney Harris
He's been following me around ever since I got back to town
我一回镇上 他就一直跟着我
Rodney harris the gangbanger
Rodney Harris 帮派的
Yeah,he was waiting for me outside of a corner store
对 他昨天等着我走出转角商店
He did that drive-by yesterday
还开车经过我身边
So you think this looks like something a gangbanger did
所以你觉得这看上去像 帮派成员干的
Is that how you'd advise me,mr Fbi
这是你给的建议吗 FBI先生?
[Door opens] Dennison: Stan
Stan
[Clears throat] [Whispers indistinctly] All right,tell him I'll be there in a minute
好吧 告诉他我就来
You're gonna have to come up with something better than a gangbanger,derek
你最好得提出 比帮派成员更好的结论 Derek
Detective gordinski,cpb
芝加哥警局Gordinski探长
You think an fbi agent,a bau profiler committed a homicide
你觉得一个FBI探员 一个BAU人物分析专家会犯一起杀人罪?
Actually,three homicides at least,over 15 years
实际上 至少是三起 历时十五年
You--you think he's a serial killer
你--你认为他是连环杀手?
This is ridiculous
太荒谬了
Has he been charged with anything
他有被起诉什么罪状吗?
I got 72 hours for that
我有72个小时准备
I'd like to see him
我想见见他
Be my guest
请便
This way
这边走
Agent gideon,right
Gideon探员 对吗?
Yes
对
I owe you a big thank you
我要好好谢谢你
I had no suspects at all until you looked over my case for me and sent me this profile
在你研究我的案子 送来人物分析之前 我一直找不到嫌犯
Everything in it points to that son of a bitch,derek morgan
所有的事实都指向那个狗娘养的 Derek Morgan
[ ] I profiled him
我描述的是他
It's all right there
就在那儿
Detective,a profile's just a guide
探长 人物分析只具导向作用
Yeah,this one guided me to him
对 这个指导我找到了他
They're really more useful in the elimination of suspects rather than the inclusion
比起寻找 他们更有利于排除嫌犯
That's not the way you presented it to me
你们给我介绍时可不是这么说的
Well,if I confused you,I'm sorry
如果迷惑了你 我很抱歉
I'm not confused at all
我一点都不迷惑
Look,whatever it is in here that made you consider agent morgan a suspect has to be coincidencE
听着 不管你如何凭借里面的内容 认为Morgan探员就是嫌犯 都一定是巧合
You can't rely solely on this
不能单凭这一点
You're right,I'm not
说的对 我并没有
[Door opens] You ok
你还好吗?
This kid
这个孩子
I was with him yesterday
昨天跟我在一起
So
然后呢?
So he's dead
死了
I drove him home,hotch,and gordinski's saying I was the last person seen with him
是我送他回家的 Hotch Gordinske说我是被目击最后和他一起的人
15 years ago,I was a new detective
15年前 我还是新进的警探
One of my first cases was a black kid
早先的案子中 就有一个黑人孩子
12 or 13 years old,found strangled in a vacant lot near here
十二三岁 扼死在一片空地上
Boy was a john doe,right
没有身份 对吗?
Still unidentified to this day
至今没有确认
Wait,a 12-year-old kid that no one reported missing
等等 没人报告一个12岁孩子失踪吗?
Ever
从来没有
Four years ago,another body turns up,same M O
四年前 另一具尸体 同样的作案手法
Worked that case just as hard,came up with just as much nothing
众多未知情况使案子十分棘手
Nobody in the area had ever seen the kid before
这一地区的人从前都没见过这个孩子
No one's looking for these kids
没人找他们吗?
Then a few months back,I attended a seminar that you taught at cpd headquarters
几个月前 我参加了 你在芝加哥警局总部举办的研究会
I told you about my case,you said to send you the files and you'd look 'em over
说了我的案子 你让我送文件给你研究
This is the profile you worked up
这是你总结的人物分析
There are about 3 million people in chicago
芝加哥有大约三百万人口
Your profile said I was looking for a black male,25 to 35,with a knowledge of the area
你在人物分析中说 要找一个黑人男性 25到35岁 熟知这里的环境
Nonthreatening to children-- either knows them or is normal enough that he doesn't scare them
对孩子没有威胁--不是互相认识 就是长相普通 不会吓到他们
A probable criminal record
很可能有犯罪记录
It also said the way the body was placed
还说 尸体都被轻放在...
gently on a mattress,not just tossed on the ground,
床垫上 并非随意丢弃在路上
indicated someone who was probably consumed with guilt,especially for the first victim
表明他怀有罪恶感 尤其是第一个受害人
Your exact words are--
你的原话是--
"with a guilt-ridden offender,"the bau postulates the first victim is the most important "
"饱受罪恶感折磨的罪犯" BAU设定首位受害人是最重要的
and the unsub may still visit the place of the crime or even the victim himself
不明人物可能还会探望犯罪地点 甚至受害人本身
" Care to guess who visits my first victim every time he's in town
有兴趣猜猜 每次回家 都会去探望受害人的是谁吗?
Can't be just visiting the victim
不止探望受害人
There has to be more than that
一定还会有其他行动
Sure
当然
You said the unsub might try to inject himself into the investigation to keep tabs on it
你说不明人物可能会试图 混进调查 进行监视
Morgan has called our headquarters many times since he joined the bureau
Morgan加入你们部门后 多次致电我们总部
Always about this case
都是有关这个案子
So,wait,he talked to you about it
等等 他跟你谈论过?
Headquarters
总部
He'd never call me
他决不会打给我
After I got your profile,I checked airline records
收到你的人物分析之后 我调查了航班纪录
Turns out derek had just left chicago when the other body turned up
结果出现第二具尸体时 Derek刚巧离开芝加哥
Tell me the story from the beginning
从头说起
I--I guess it starts when I was 15
我 我想应该是从十五岁时开始
I was coming home from football practice one day
一天 我橄榄球训练结束后回家
[Car horn blares] Me and my boy,we were goofing off,
我和我的伙伴正在玩耍
you know,we were throwing a football around
你知道我们在扔球
[Telephone ringing] The only person that I'd ever seen dead before that was my father
这之前我看过唯一的死去的人 就是我的父亲
when I was ten
就在我十岁那年
I mean,there I was,I was looking at this kid and he was my own age,hotch
我是说 我在那儿 看着他 他就和我一般大Hotch
Dead in this vacant lot
在那个空旷的场地里死去
And he was never identified
他身份不明
Nobody knew who he was,nobody ever even reported him missing
没人知道他是谁 没人报告过他失踪
And that,that just didn't sit right with me
而那人跟我并没关系
So I--I felt responsible for him,I mean,I was the one that found him,right
所以--我觉得对他有责任 我是说 我就是找到他的人
I went around the neighborhood,door to door,trying to start a collection,
我挨家挨户的募捐
and... eventually I got enough so I could bury him,and... I gave him a little headstone
最后... 凑足钱葬了他 ... 我还给他建了块墓碑
What did you put on the headstone if he wasn't identified
既然他身份不明 那你在墓碑上写了什么
Morgan: Just the date
只写了日期
I left room for a name if he was ever identified
我留了地方写他的名字 如果有一天他被确定了身份
And you still visit him
你现在还去拜祭他吗
Hotch,I go see this kid every time I'm home
Hotch 每次我回家都会去拜祭他
I just feel like he deserves to have somebody look in on him
我只是觉得应该有人去拜祭他
Gordinski must read that as a guilty conscience,a killer revisiting his victim
Gordinski 一定觉得这是你的愧疚作祟 凶手去拜祭受害者
But that can't be the only reason he suspects you
但这不可能是他怀疑你的唯一理由
Believe me,that guy's had it in for me my entire life
相信我 那家我盯了我一辈子了
He's supremely confident that you're his killer
他非常自信你就是那个杀手
Then yesterday another kid ends up dead and the last person he was with was derek morgan
昨天又一个孩子死了 而最后见他的人就是Derek Morgan
In the boy's pocket we found one of his fbi business cards,
在这孩子的一个口袋里 我们发现了一张FBI 的名片
his cell number written on the back of it
他的手机号在背后
In fact,every time morgan's in town,he hangs out with kids
事实上 每次Morgan 在镇上 他都和孩子们混在一起
This is all just coincidence
这都是巧合
A hell of a lot of coincidences
他妈的巧合还真是多
It's purely circumstantial
虽然很充分 但无法证实
So's a fingerprint
指纹也是这样
Did I mention that morgan found the body in 1991
我告诉过你们Morgan 在 1991 年发现尸体的事了吗
Hidden way back in a vacant lot
被藏在一片废弃的场地内
Now,don't you teach that when a body is hard to find,
你不是说尸体很难被找到吗
the person finding it is always a suspect
发现尸体的人总是嫌疑犯
Reid: There are key pieces of the profile that don't fit,detective
有一个重要分析不符合 探长
Uh,the age,25 to 35,morgan was 15 or so at the time
年龄介于25 和35 Morgan 那时大约15 岁
Also says that age is the hardest to predict,
你还说年龄是很难预言的
and I should never exclude someone simply because of a discrepancy with the age
我不能仅仅因为年龄不符 就排除谁
What about the speculation
那么推测呢
that since he didn't managed to leave any evidence at the scene of the crime
因为他在案发现称没有留下任何证据
and he most likely has a criminal record or previous law enforcement knowledge
所以他得有犯罪纪律 和法律知识
Derek wasn't even in the bureau yet when the first body was found
Derek 发现尸体的时候 他还没有进调查局呢
He may not have had a knowledge of law enforcement
他可能没有法律知识
but derek morgan definitely had a criminal record
但是Derek Morgan 的的确确有犯罪记录
A desperate detective here
我们的对手是个绝望的探长
Three dead boys,no evidence at all,
三个死去的孩子 完全没有证据
so he applies the profile directly to someone he already suspected
他把分析直接用于他已经怀疑的人身上
It's easy to get tunnel vision that way
这样很容易让人视野狭窄
One begins to twist facts to suit theories instead of theories to suit facts
将事实强加于理论 而非将理论运用于事实
That's,uh,one of sherlock holmes's favorite quotes
这是福尔摩斯最喜欢引用的话
We need to figure out who really killed these boys before they decide to charge morgan
在他们决定起诉Morgan前 我们必须查处是谁杀了这些孩子
What do you want us to do
你想让我们怎么做
Last victim was someone morgan was seen with
最后一个受害者被 看见与Morgan在一起
Conveniently,morgan was already a suspect in the other two
凑巧的是 Morgan 已经是另两起谋杀案的嫌犯了
Someone set him up
有人陷害了他
We should consider morgan a victim
我们应该把Morgan当作受害者
Prentiss,you and reid talk to his family,learn about him--
Prentiss 你和Reid 去和他的家人谈谈 找一些他的资料
especially around the time of the first murder
尤其是第一起谋杀案时期的资料
Do we have the address
我们有地址吗
I can take you
我可以带你去
Oh,that's ok
哦 没关系的
Gideon: No Actually,that's not a bad idea
不 事实上这主意不错
Right
好吧
Okey-doke,lead the way,detective
好吧 带路吧 探长
According to morgan,he's got a bad history with gordinski
据Morgan所说 他和Gordinski关系不好
He's got a bad history generally
总的来说他的过去不怎么光彩
Resisting arrest,vandalism,aggravated battery
拒捕 破坏公物 重伤罪
This is morgan
这就是Morgan
As a juvenile Look at the dates
看看日期 是个青少年
This isn't in his personnel file
这不是他的人事档案
He said he told me everything relevant
他说该说的他都说了
Then he either lied or he doesn't consider this relevant
他要么是在撒谎 要么是觉得这无关紧要
Since when is the criminal history of a suspect not relevant
从什么时候起嫌犯的犯罪记录 变成无关紧要了
You just called him a suspect
你刚刚称他为嫌疑犯
Get garcia into morgan's life
让Garcia 查查Morgan的生平
Yes,sir
是
Hey,hotch,I almost forgot
嘿 Hotch 我差点忘了
There's a local banger out here,his name is rodney harris
当地有个混混 他叫Rodney harris
He's been running these streets for a while now
他混在这一带有些日子了
You have a criminal record
你有犯罪记录
What
什么
Where did you get this
你从哪里弄到的
What difference does that make
这有什么不同吗
Hotch... this was supposed to be expunged
Hotch... 这份资料应该被删除的
My record's clean
我的记录很干净
I asked you if there was anything you hadn't told me
我问过你有没有什么没告诉我的
A judge expunged this,it doesn't exist anymore,man
法官删除了上面的记录 这不会再存在了
I was a kid,it's nothing
我当时是个孩子 这没什么
Aggravated battery
重伤
I-- [Sighs] Ok
我...好吧
I was with some guys,we got in a fight with some other guys
我和一群孩子在一起 我们在和另一群人打架
Rodney,this cat I'm trying to tell you about,it was him
Rodney 我要告诉你的那个人 就是他
We got into it a little bit,we knocked each other around,
我们有点过火了 都把对方打倒在地
he got a couple stitches in his head so they made it aggravated
他头上缝了几针 所以他们定位重伤
That's it
就是这样
So you're saying this rodney committed three murders because you beat him up
所以你是说Rodney 杀了三个人 就是因为你打了他
No
不
I'm saying he's been following me around since I got here,
我是说自从我到这里来 他就一直跟踪我
so go talk to him and you might get something
去找他谈谈 你会有所收获的
This was expunged
这记录已经被删除了
You still should've told me
你还是得告诉我
You know how important accurate information is to victimology
你知道掌握准确的信息 对受害人研究的重要性
Whoa
哇
Victimology
受害人研究
It's very likely the latest victim was an attempt to set you up
最近的一个受害者很可能是为了陷害你
Are you profiling me
你在分析我吗
Morgan,we need to look at-- no
- Morgan 我们得谈谈 - 不
We don't need to do anything
我们什么都不需要做
Derek,you're in trouble here
Derek 你有麻烦了
[Laughs] Hotch,I didn't do this
Hotch 我没干过
I am not worried about gordinski out there
我才不怕Gordinski呢
You still have three dead children
你还有三个死去的孩子
Ok,ok,so you profile them
好吧 那么你分析他们
That's the case
那才是案件
Is there something else you don't want us to find out about
是不是有什么你不想让我们查到的事情
Hotch,I don't need the people I work with going into my entire world
Hotch 我不需要我的同事 对我的事情如数家珍
Is,uh,derek all right
Derek 还好吧
He wouldn't let us go down there
他不让我们去看他
He's fine
他很好
Our boss is with him
我们头和他在一起
Did he tell you gordinski's been harassing him since he was a kid
他告诉你了没 从小时候起 Gordinski就一直骚扰他
Reid: Why's that
为什么
You'd have to ask that bastard
你得去问那个混蛋
Oh,sarah
哦 Sarah
It's true,mom
这是事实 妈妈
Sure it is
当然是
What are you even doing in my mother's house
你们到我母亲家来干什么
They asked me
他们要我来的
Oh,really
真的吗
I don't understand how they could think he did this
我不明白他们怎么会觉得是他干的
Someone may be trying to make it look like he hurt those kids
有人陷害了他
And the police believe it
警察相信吗
Just following the evidence
只是跟着证据走
But he's an fbi agent
但他是个FBI探员
Reid: Actually... law enforcement officials
事实上... 执法者
are just as probable statistically to commit a crime as anyone else
犯罪的几率和普通人一样
Look at the cross-section of a society,there's a general population
看看社会的剖面 有一类人群
and a small fraction-- he's not actually saying
- 和一小部分... - 他并不是说
we believe derek's involved in this
我们相信Derek涉嫌其中
Oh,no,no,yeah,not at all
不 不 不 完全不是
I'm merely,um-- speaking theoretically
我只是...从理论的角度说
You're dr Reid,right
你是Reid博士 对吗
Mm-hm
嗯
Derek talks about you
Derek说起过你
He does
真的吗
Anyway,so... someone may be trying to make it look like this was derek
不管怎样... 可能有人想要陷害Derek
But derek loves kids
但是Derek 很爱孩子
Every time he's here,he goes to the youth center
每次他回来 都要去青少年中心
Youth center
青少年中心
The upward youth center
上进青少年中心
Does that have some sort of significance for him
对他有什么特别之处吗
Oh... are you saying there's something in it for him
哦... 你是说从中他会得到好处吗
Other than giving back to the poor kids of your neighborhood
而不是看望社区里的可怜孩子
Sarah... sarah,we're friends of your brother'S
Sarah... Sarah 我们是你哥哥的朋友
We're here trying to help
我们来这是为了帮忙
When we ask a question,it isn't to denigrate or demean anything he's done
我们问问题 并不是想要 诋毁或者贬低他做的事
We just have to know everything,so we can figure out where to look next
我们只是想要知道所有的事 好让我们知道下一步怎么办
Is there some special significance to the youth center
那个青少年中心对他有什么特别之处吗
The youth center saved his life
那个青少年中心挽救了他
Does this make any sense to you
你想通了吗
No
没
He's clearly hiding something else
他一定在隐藏什么
Well,we know he isn't involved in any murders
我们只知道他不涉嫌谋杀
No
不
There are larger implications
还有更重要的是
We can't have people on this team who have secrets
我们不允许团队中的队员有秘密
Oh,come on,hotch,we all have secrets
哦 算了吧 Hotch 我们都有秘密
Would you want us profiling you
你想要我们分析你吗
I feel terrible looking into his life like this
我讨厌像这样窥看他的生活
I know,just remember we're trying to help him
我知道 但记住我们是在帮他
Garcia: Right,ok
好吧
Graduated with honors from northwestern law
从西北法学院荣誉毕业
Did you know he was a star football player
你知道他以前是个橄榄球星吗
Surprisingly,I don't know much about him at all
十分惊诧 我对他了解得不多
Quarterback
四分后位
That's the guy who throws the ball,right
就是那个扔球的对吗
Yes
没错
Ha That's what he was
哈 他就是
Full ride athletic scholarship
全额运动员奖学金
Sophomore year he severely injured his left knee and he never played again
大二时左膝盖严重受伤 从此不再打球
Ok,garcia,look further back,ok
好了 Garcia 看看过去的
Before college
大学以前
Garcia: Right Where are we
好的 我们到哪了
Ok,um... wait
好了... 等等
He was mentioned in the chicago register as...
他在芝加哥注册过...
body of a ch-child in a vacant lot in 1991
1991年 一具在空旷场地上发现的男孩尸体
[Sighs] That's our first victim
那是我们第一个受害者
Garcia: He never told me about this
他从来没跟我说过
He never told any of us
他谁也没告诉
My husband,um,their father,was killed when he tried to stop a robbery
我的丈夫 也就是他们的父亲 在阻止一起劫案时被杀了
Derek was with him,he was ten
Derek 那时和他在一起 他当时十岁
A year or so later,he started getting into trouble
大概一年以后 他开始卷入麻烦了
What kind of trouble
什么样的麻烦
He started running around with older kids
他开始和大孩子混在一起
They would give him money to run errands for them
他们给他钱让他为他们跑腿
Not drugs
不是毒品
No,derek would never disgrace his father's name
不是 Derek绝不会辱没他爸爸的名声
But they were gangbangers
但他们是个帮派
So people started looking at derek like he was one of them
所以大家把Derek看成他们中的一员
One night,he and a friend were attacked by some boys from another gang
一天晚上 他和他朋友 被其他帮派的孩子们袭击
Big fight
打得很凶
And one of the other boy's head split open
其中一个男孩的头被打破
And that was the first time gordinski arrested him
那是Gordinski第一次抓他
Now,he wasn't a detective yet,just a street cop,
那时他还不是探员 只是个巡逻警察
but from that night on,no matter what happened in the neighborhood,he'd pick derek up for it
从那时起 不管邻里发生了什么事 他都会怪罪于Derek
Dennison: Probably because he was involved
可能是因为他确实有份参与
The hell he was
该死的不可能
Stan's never arrested anyone who didn't need arresting
Stan从没有抓错过人
He did with derek
他抓错了Derek
Until carl buford stepped in
直到Carl Buford介入
Carl buford
Carl Buford?
He runs a youth center
他开了个青少年中心
He took derek under his wing
他保护Derek
Mentored him
教导他
Became like a surrogate father
就像是代理父亲
He taught him football and that changed derek's life
他教他橄榄球 这也改变了Derek的人生
He got a scholarship to college,with it he got his degree
他得到了大学奖学金 又拿到学位
Where is carl buford now
Carl Buford现在在哪?
He still runs the youth center
还是在青少年中心里工作
I'd like to talk to him
我要和他谈谈
Detective,do you think you could take me over there
探员 能带我过去吗?
Just you
只有你?
Yeah
是的
I thought maybe you could stay here and keep going through this stuff
你还是留在这里 继续搞定这事吧
Good idea
好主意
Yeah,keep going through the stuff
继续搞定这事
Is there a criminal history
有犯罪历史吗?
Garcia: Criminal
犯罪?
Garcia,is there a criminal history
Garcia 他有犯罪历史吗?
Jj,there's not gonna be a-- [Computer beeps] There's a sealed file
不可能吧... 有个被密封的档案
Unseal it
那就打开
But it's a sealed file
但这是密封档案
Garcia,helping him
Garcia 帮帮他
Ah
啊
Right
好吧
Helping him,helping him... that's a juvenile criminal record
帮他 是在帮他 是青少年犯罪记录
It was expunged and sealed by a judge esposito
但已被Esposito法官消除并密封
after presentation of a letter and testimonial from a local youth center director
因为一位当地青少年中心导师的 一封信和证词
"Finest young man I've ever known,
"他是我见过最好的孩子"
"criminal record could jeopardize "potential scholarship offers...
"犯罪记录会破坏他拿奖学金的机会"
stake my personal and professional reputation..."
"我以我个人职业名誉做保证"
garcia: He was definitely a fan of our boy
他一定是Derek的粉丝
Do we have a name
他叫什么?
Hang on a second
等等
I'm carl buford
我是Carl Buford
I've brought damien walters' mother to see detective gordinski
我带Damien Walters的母亲来见Gordinski探员
Hi,carl
嗨 Carl
Stan
Stan
Mrs Walters,thanks for coming
Walters夫人 谢谢您能来
This way
这边走
Buford
Buford
Did you just say buford
你刚刚说Buford?
would you just give me the hell out here
你能把我救出去吗?
That wouldn't be a good idea,would it
恐怕不是好主意
Says who
谁说的
Apparently I provided the profile that led them to arrest you
很明显 是我提供了人物分析 让他们逮捕了你
You what
你做了什么?
They sent the case to me a few months ago
几个月前 他们把这个案子寄给我
I did a routine consult but he was looking for it to lead to you
我做了些常规咨询 但他一心希望分析出的人就是你
Preconception of guilt
他有偏见 认为我有罪
We just can't force 'em to let you go,it's not gonna look too good with the local press
我们不能逼他们放了你 最好还是和当地媒体搞好关系
Oh,like I give a damn about the press,gideon
好像我很在乎他们一样 Gideon
Well,we cannot appear to be covering something up
我们看上去 不能像是在掩饰什么
You trying to say something to me right now
你想要说什么?
Only if you're hiding something You need to trust us
除非你对我们有所隐瞒 你得相信我们
Trust us enough to tell us about it
信任我们 告诉我们全部真相
Gideon
Gideon
It's not about trust
这和信任无关
It's about having a little privacy
我只想有些个人隐私
I got the right to keep something to myself
我有权利对自己保密
Look at us,man,we practically live together already
看看我们 我们几乎已住在一起
Then the best way to clear you is...find the real unsub
那排除你嫌疑的最好方法是... 找出真正的凶手
Find anything out about morgan
有查到Morgan什么吗?
The record wasn't picked up in his background check
背景资料里没有犯罪记录
because everything in it was expunged and the file sealed by a judge
因为犯罪记录都被消除了 档案也被法官密封
Forgiving judge
仁慈的法官
It was based on the recommendation
这是因为社区里一位正直人士的推荐信
of an upstanding member of the community who took personal responsibility for morgan
并以个人保证负责Morgan
That sounds like somebody we should talk to for more background
似乎我们得跟那人谈谈 多得到些背景信息
Should be easy,he's right over there
应该很简单 他就在那
Hello
你好
Mr Buford
Buford先生
This guy's been honored by everybody but the nobel society
这个人真是倍受尊敬 就差没得诺贝尔奖
That's carl buford
这就是Carl Buford
Who are you
你是谁?
I'm with the fbi
我是FBI
Do you know derek morgan
你认识Derek Morgan吗?
Yeah,he's a friend of mine
恩 他是我朋友
I've been trying to call him
我一直想打电话给他
He's a little busy right now
他现在有点忙
Is there something I can do to help you
我能帮你吗?
I just... a friend of mine
我只是... 我的一个朋友
Someone killed him yesterday
昨天被人杀害了
Do you know something about who might have done it
你知道是谁做的吗?
No
不
Derek's always telling me if I need somebody to talk to,about anything,I can call him
Derek总是说 如果我想找人谈 任何事情 都可以找他
Guess I just wanted to... I don't know
我只是想... 我也不知道
I'll tell you what
这样吧
Why don't you give me your name and I'll let him know that you've been trying to reach him
你告诉我名字 我去跟他说你一直在找他
James barfield
James Barfield
Does he know where to find you
他知道怎么联系你吗?
He can find me here
他可以来这里找我
Anytime
任何时间?
All the time
随时都行
You folks work with derek morgan
你们和Derek Morgan一起工作?
Yes,sir,closely
是的 关系非常亲近
You knew him well as a teenager
他青少年时 你就很了解他吧
One of the finest boys I ever coached
他是我教过最好的孩子之一
Football
橄榄球
I run a youth center
我开了个青少年中心
I gather you were instrumental in helping to get his criminal records expunged
据我调查 你提供了很大帮助 消除他的犯罪记录
I feel terrible about that now
我现在觉得很后悔
You do
你这么觉得?
Well,in view of what's happened
鉴于现在发生的事
What's happened is a mistake
现在发生的 都是个错误
I'm confused,I thought stan said there was all kinds of evidence
我糊涂了 Stan说有充足的证据
There is
确实有
Thanks,carl,you can take miss walters home now
谢谢Carl 你可以送Walters女士回家了
Appreciate you bringing her in
非常感谢你带她来
Of course,of course
不用客气
Derek morgan
Derek Morgan
It's still hard for me to believe
我还是不能相信
For them,too
他们也不能
I can understand that
我很理解
Derek had a way of charming people into looking past his deficiencies
Derek就是很有办法 迷惑别人忽略他的不足之处
Excuse me,deficiencies
你说什么不足之处?
Well,you've seen the records
你们也看过那些记录了
Derek was at the youth center yesterday,wasn't he
Derek昨天在青少年中心 是吗?
Playing football with damien walters and some other boys
和Damien Walters还有其他男孩玩橄榄球
Carl's the one that saw 'em leaving together
Carl看见他们一起离开的
Did you talk to him
你跟他说话了吗?
I was working inside
我在里面工作
By the time I was done,they were leaving
等我做好时 他们已走了
When was the last time you did talk to him
你上次和他讲话什么时候?
I don't know
不知道
Years
好多年了
If you need anything else,stan
如果你需要什么 尽管说 Stan
Anything at all
任何东西
Thanks,carl
谢谢 Carl
Appreciate it
感激不尽
You seem friendly with mr Buford
你好像和Buford先生关系很好
I can't tell you how many times that guy's come through for me
他不知道帮助我成功了多少次
Goin' way back to my beat cop days
当我还是片警的时候
Carl buford knows the kids in this neighborhood better than almost anybody
Carl Buford比所有人都更了解这里的孩子
He's knocked more than a few of them back onto the straight and narrow
他教诲了很多孩子 带他们回正道
Has he kept up with the investigation
他有跟进调查吗?
I'm sorry
你说什么?
Over the years,does he ask how it's going
这些年来 他有问案件的进展如何吗?
Yeah,he'S... wait a second,you're not gonna try to turn this off on him to save your guy,are you
恩 他有... 等等 你不会想要靠怀疑他来救你们的人吧
Just a question
问问而已
Carl buford is a local hero
Carl Buford是这里的英雄
I'm sure he is
我知道他是
Carl buford
Carl Buford
What
什么?
Carl buford,he runs the youth center
Carl Buford 开青少年中心的
What's that got to do with anything
那有什么关系?
He's responsible for getting your records expunged
他负责担保 清除你的犯罪记录
I told you to stay the hell out of my business
我告诉你别管我的事
You said you visit the youth center every time you come here
你说你每次回来 都会去青少年中心
So what
那又怎样?
Buford says he hasn't spoken to you in years
Buford说你们好几年没说话了
Why don't you visit the man who made your career possible
为什么你不拜访这位 促成你成功事业的人呢?
Damn you,hotch
该死 Hotch
It is none of your damn business
这不管你的事
Buford's the one who told detectives you were with damien
是Buford告诉探员 你和Damien在一起
I am warning you,hotch
我警告你 Hotch
Back off
别管这事
I'm not saying it's mr Buford
我没说凶手是Buford先生
There's a huge amount of investigation left to be done
还有很多调查要做
For 15 years he hasn't been the slightest bit suspicious
15年来 他没有一点嫌疑
Morgan won't even talk about buford
Morgan不肯谈Buford的事
He won't
他不肯?
Buford should be that kid's hero
Buford可是他的英雄
Something happened
一定有事情发生
You talking about carl buford
你们在说Carl Buford?
Yes
是的
We just left his office
我们刚离开他的办公室
Dennison: Hey
嘿
What,did we turn him loose
怎么了 我们放了他?
You let him escape
你让他逃跑了?
black male,33,six foot one,name is derek morgan
黑人男子 33岁 6尺1寸 名叫Derek Morgan
You're standing there trying to convince me
你们现在是想让我相信
that a local hero is my killer while you let my suspect dance our the back door
当地的英雄是凶手 而我的嫌疑犯却逍遥法外?
I'm gonna charge all of your asses
我要告你们这些白痴!
Yes,as soon as possible
对 尽快
You have to tell your officers that morgan's not a threat
你必须告诉你的警察 Morgan不构成威胁
Like hell I will
你觉得我会吗?
But this-- lady,as far as I'm concerned,he is a threat,ok
- 但是... - 女士 在我看来 他是个威胁
They're beyond reason
他们完全不讲理
We have to find hm first
我们得先找到他
Any ideas
有什么办法吗?
His mother said that buford practically raised him after his father died,
他妈妈说 自从他爸死后 几乎是Buford养大了他
he mentored him,took him on trips,spent all of his time with him
他教导他 带他旅行 所有时间都陪他
Basically became a surrogate father
基本上就是个代理父亲
Jason,I think I know what he was afraid we'd find
Jason 我想我知道他害怕我们发现什么了
Detective,we may know where he's heading
探员 我们可能知道他在哪
Lookin' good there,kid
看起来不错 孩子
I was tryin' to call you
我一直想打电话给你
I'm here now
我在这里
Someone killed damien
Damien被杀了
I know
我知道
James,we need to talk about carl buford
James 我们要谈谈Carl Buford
What about him
关于什么?
You're a star player,right
你是明星球员 对吗?
Center of attention
中心人物
Yeah,I guess
我想是的
You know,I used to be that guy
知道吗 我以前也是
Yeah,I know
我知道
It's a lot of pressure,isn't it
压力很大 对吗?
Always wanna make 'em happy
总想让他们高兴
Impress 'em
给他们留下印象
I can handle it
我能处理好
Oh,I'm sure you can,kid
哦 我知道你肯定行 孩子
Does he ever take you to his cabin
他带你去过他的小屋吗?
What
什么?
Fishin' in wisconsin,camping
在威斯康星河钓鱼 野营
Do things you wish you had a real father for
做一些 你希望由亲身父亲带你做的事
Sometimes
有时会
Yeah,he's good like that
对 他那样很好
You know about the cabin
你知道小屋
James,i told you,I used to be you
James 我说过 我过去跟你一样
What do you mean
什么意思?
The first time you weren't even sure what was goin' on
第一次 你甚至不确定是怎么回事
He brushed up against you
他碰你
You thought it might have just been an accident
你以为那也许只是意外
But then at the cabin,he let you sit and drink with him
但后来在小屋 他让你坐下 跟他喝酒
You thought it was kinda cool
你觉得这很酷
Made you feel grown
让你觉得自己长大了
He gave you a glass of wine
他给了你一杯葡萄酒
Maybe a little shot of something harder
也许更烈一点
And then he took you swimming
然后带你游泳
Only he told you to jump in without your swimsuit on
只是 他让你别穿泳裤跳下去
He did things to you,james,didn't he
他对你做过 James 对吗?
He did 'em to me,too
也对我做过
You do whatever you think you gotta do to keep him happy
你觉得无论如何必须让他高兴
because he's the closest thing to a father you got
因为他最像你的父亲
But what he's doin' to you is wrong
但他的所作所为是错的
And you don't have to let it continue,man
不该让它继续下去 孩子
- Yeah,I do
- 不 我要 - 不能
My oldest brother's in jail,my sister was paralyzed in a drive-by,she's eight years old
我的长兄在监狱 我妹妹 在一次帮派游行中瘫痪 她只有八岁
I'm all my mom's got left
我是我妈妈所有的希望
I gotta get us outta here
我必须让全家离开这
Carl's gonna make sure I get into college
Carl能确保我进大学
Then I can make something of myself
然后我就能有所作为
James,you are something,man
James 你很重要
You're something right here,right now,without carl buford
就在此时此刻 没有Carl Buford 你依然很重要
You just gotta believe that
只要相信这点
Where's carl right now,huh
现在Carl在哪儿 哈?
Look at you,man
看看你 孩子
You're out here in the dark running pass routes
天黑了还在这儿练跑传球路线
That's you
这就是你
That ain't got nothin' to do with carl
跟Carl没有一点关系
What you got inside of here,that's what's gonna get you off these streets
这里的东西会让你摆脱这里的街道
You never told
你从没说过
Not until right now
之前没有
Damien always said I should call you
Damien总说 我该给你电话
What
什么?
Damien knew
Damien知道?
I didn't think you'd believe me
我觉得你不会相信我
James... I got your back
James...我支持你
Forever
永远
Carl
Carl
You've been let go
你被释放了
Looks that way
看来是的
I told 'em it was crazy,thinkin' you were involved in any killing
我就说他们疯了 尽然认为你会杀人
Really
真的?
Gordinski said you're the one who told 'em I drove damien home
Gordinski说你告诉他们 是我送Damien回家的
Was that supposed to be a secret
那应该保密吗?
No
不
That wasn'T
不是
I don't follow
我不明白
All these years,I kept my mouth shut
一直以来 我闭口不谈
I let you go on being a hero
让你继续做一个英雄
Carl buford,my mentor
Carl Buford 我的导师
What are you talkin' about
你要说什么?
God,I was so afraid of you
上帝 我以前好怕你
I was afraid of the police,afraid of losing everything I was gaining
怕警察 怕失去我拥有的一切
But that's how you work,isn't it
但你就是这样控制的 是吗?
You make sure there's a hell of a lot to lose,don't you
确保别人要失去很多东西 是吗?
I don't know what you think you remember
我不知道你记得什么
No,no,no See,it's not what I remember that's gonna hurt you,carl
别 看 我记得的不会伤害你 Carl
Our business is over way too long ago to matter
我们之间的事已经过了太久 再提也没用了
You're protected by a statute of limitations and that's my fault
你受追诉期保护 是我的错
Then good night
那就晚安
You set me up
你陷害我
You knew damien walters wanted james to call me about you
你知道Damien Walters 想让James举报你
So you killed him
于是就杀了他
You killed him because you knew I'd come after you,didn't you
因为你知道我会来质问你 对吗?
Now you're just talking crazy
简直是无稽之谈
God,I should have told somebody about you when I was a kid
上帝 我小时候就该举报你
When you were helping me
就在你还在帮我的时候
Well,you know what happens in cases like this
知道通常这类案件会怎么样吗?
Once that dam breaks,the flood comes
一旦决口 就会一泻千里
One kid steps up,just one
只要一个孩子站出来
And then another one,and another
就会一个接一个
Because they're not scared of you anymore
因为他们都不再怕你
They know they're not alone
他们知道自己并不孤单
James barfield is your dam
James Barfield就是那个坝
Whatever lies james told you... they're not lies
- 不管James对你说了什么谎... - 那不是谎话
You did the same thing to me
你对我也做过同样的事
I did nothing to you,to james
我什么也没做 不管是对你 还是James
One by one,they're gonna pile up until there's so many accusations
一个接一个 直到有足够多的指控
- You can't say that they're all lies
你不能说他们都在说谎
any idea how many kids I've helped get out of this neighborhood
你知道 我帮助多少孩子 走出这个社区吗?
Hm
嗯?
How many lives I've provided
我养活了多少人?
Look at yo 
看看你 今天的成就
yeah,well,it wasn't for free,was it
对 但那不是免费的 对吗?
I pulled you out of the gutter
我帮你离开贫民区
I pulled myself out of the gutter,all the way to the fbi
我自己离开的贫民区 一路走进了FBI
I did that
是我做成的
You sayin' I had nothin' to do with making you who you are
你是说 你长成现在这样 我没有一点贡献
No,carl
不是 Carl
Actually I'm saying you have everything to do with making me who I am
事实上 我是说 现在的我都是拜你所赐
Because of you I'm somebody who gets to spend the rest of this life
因为你 我的余生都要...
making sure guys like you go down
让像你这样的家伙下地狱
Look,derek... carl: I never hurt you
听着 Derek...我从没伤害过你
You could have said no
你可以说不的
You're under arrest,carl
Carl 你被捕了
I've helped a lot of kids
我帮助了很多孩子
Let's go
走吧
The neighborhood won't be the same without me
没有我 这个社区不会像现在这样
It's gonna be worse without the center
没有这个中心 会更糟的
Somebody'll keep this center running
有人会让这个中心继续下去
The neighborhood will
这个社区会
I will
我也会
Wait Wait
等等
DereK... isn't there something you can do for me
Derek...你能帮帮我吗?
You go to hell
下地狱吧你